remember really like that if happen I
miss Catholic is this life I was like
huge like nobody can't comfort I was
trying I can't tell you because it's
just to share that
I think that'd be too hard to hit
tonight yeah she has pulled in Taj it
this girl you do really quick now you
really would
laughs that was weird all right Scotties
I hope none of y'all are taking pole
dancing class now pole dancing class is
cool I take it back
yeah that's right super cool no no
that's like it depends why well it's
just like have fun and like get a good
yeah no no I mean guys people looking
for attention and that's good I don't
think so cause you don't really get
attention from your pole classes lately
posted online like the kind of girl
who's standing on the table at the club
right all right guys so we're driving
the first what did you yeah
don't discriminate you're right you're
right Eddie what i discriminate against
he said don't discriminate gee somehow
my discriminating against I think women
dance attention whores
oh absolutely discriminate against
attention whores I am at which stop
though I don't know if you guys follow
me on Twitch but I'm a quick start
so guy offered me $4 to show my left
nipple I'd really thought about doing
yeah why wouldn't you
this is the first comma planning retreat
yeah it's not the first time a retreat
yes that's right
George memory you're gonna change your
wardrobe to wifebeaters you retell the
scope he's about that no no I put a
wife-beater on I looked at myself in the
mirror and what camp Baylor can't do it
guys guess what we're driving on right
now the new model
well the meanwhile so good
the new model is so much better so it's
trained on some toyota data now trying
on tour today to try it on HDR data oh
that's good that's good
yes and this is the caller planning
retreat yeah eta for new model by the
way now you tell them never never know
the model is just for us actually no
chips next week guys
Tesla data next Friday
stop and go yet for what stop ago
certainly works in your Center nine
you're out for but don't worry cuz
yeah no new model ships Friday GM ships
Friday and Bosch Wow
what's out there yeah
that's the scope is how the quality of
the Baldy gun has the quality you guys
so magical well no not if the quality I
guess he guess who they get the article
today that's all you want to
surprisingly attractive on the inside
thank you
I agree how did you like it it's really
nice um I think if you take a slice of
it it looks nice but as a whole I just I
don't see like the you know it's not
fully cookies it I would say if I just
like staring at this section of the
whole thing is just feels no this is
such a nice car look at these back seems
like too many distinct parts put
together doesn't feel like a one thing
too bad about the exterior the exterior
is perfect
what George Nick did alone
whoa
you know we really got tired of having
your that handheld stuff
we're driving to the offside we're
driving the offside it's in lovely
Pacifica invite the stokke you know
[Laughter]
we've 74 viewers damn bras open though
everybody check out okay
all right guys I'm gonna say this on
periscope but you got all be chill about
can all discovery be chill about
something mate go to news dot y
combinator calm go to that just that
website you gotta type it in go to the
second page casually browse the links
and if you see anything that catches
your fancy after clicking on the link be
sure to upload it
that's right I'm not sure it's gonna be
on the second page
no might be on the first page the third
page but just you know casual this is
not for dates gains are filtered out
in the orange message beat jesus take
the wheel no we're a serious company
always serious products what's the
website news dot y combinator calm it's
called hacker news you haven't created
an account I would like to do a lot of
new accounts
that's G going to China they know you're
going to China DVD never mind smallest
socks
this is the new model maybe not good
surprise say he was gonna reboot it
is it the new model Oh
meanwhile has bugs still it is much
better on the highway though on the
Honda Civic the wobble is gone and the
GM the wobble is going like for some
stretches of highway when I was driving
yesterday you can't tell whether it's
the new model or Cooper's damn
so feel superhuman
das yeah it's on here it's on your
commitment this morning it is
George did you eat rice yeah whatever
type of I'm excited for a new model fu
GD ing yeah we're planning what I told
everyone I'm fine it's a long saga talk
I'll settle for regular human he's very
good no one really knows his name buddy
is very good that's right the iteration
speed is unparalleled
[Laughter]
we've got more new models in the last
two weeks that we did the last year drag
mode on , who's drag mug someone's
wondering what's going on with huevos
oh wait wait this is something this is
actually well new model be the same as
old when a road isn't mad
yeah yeah no maps maps are gonna be
later I'm Malcolm Smith mellow guy is
actually ml George the new head of ml
you scope these yeah I would love to be
had I would love to be out of ml but I
actually I write firmware and do you see
my hand I've been thinking I reaffirm
where until we finally kick ass former
engineer if any of you guys know Benny
has to send an email to give me a job at
kamidana you check out our no leverage
yeah we're hiring page now lines
everything connect you can apply
directly through lever all right so
let's see if it's actually wobbles there
we go someone found it
all right bitch nope oh my god yeah
don't post a link that's per gate don't
post the link Oh
but yeah look at the look at the
stability I've never seen the Toyota
Drive like this
yeah this feels so much better he's much
more then this has been here yeah this
is yeah exactly
this feels so much better damn it's
drifting No
that's
okay it's drifting out of the lanes fix
the model Googler cama cama owes us free
food so if you're buying a good look for
free food you should keep in mind
economist
great look at the right lane this is
this model doesn't work at all
[Music]
I know it's working
take it back to our internal tools
debugging and adjust our we should keep
a baby should know what time yeah I
played did you did you watch the barber
theist talk from last week it's all
about it's all about the tools for
labeling and no software - something's
wrong you've got a waffle add more
examples it doesn't Rebecca Liz talk
the problem wasn't as bad at this price
wasn't civic no no this car the weariest
has the worst wall but this is where's
the Civic you were really a Batman
this feels a lot better on this girl
what was that weird smile there was that
spawn where it actually just best-off
yeah
the new model doesn't have bias issues
we've removed the bias from our models
guys
we hired a diversity I've seen guys
doing it again it's doing it again the
right lanes broken look at
[Music]
did you fix that or did it fix it
guys can't ship it never mind who
said the new vana was coming out Friday
night it's failing internal QA Bailey
people are sad yeah we're sad to risotto
gonna get bad guys
my rap for dinner they grab a bunch
right behind this trough Lowe's truck on
the road
like it said yeah it's pushing out yeah
just wants to hop
somehow Glenn Hubbard
going real slow or what if the model has
learned to map and it's just trying to
change lanes for you
wrong back no new model is not specific
to
that new model is actually worse on raft
and that's part of the problem
so was asking what causes that Lane to
push out I guess my new model is
personal because the rav is now in a
different place
Etan goal coverage map so we can drive
alternative routes
only us
well actually I'll tell you when we'll
have global coverage map when somebody
else pays heart yeah like if someone
would like to like pay us money to map
their country like their country like if
Mexico paid us to map Mexico we'd map
Mexico around Mexico we would map Canada
that's right we had to fly to fly
they'll be kind of hard cuz we'd
probably drive out of the car yeah yeah
well no will you fly hurt a lot of
people will just drive it for us and
then we'll yeah so if the country or a
company would like to pay us from after
that country that is possible
a really weak right now
[Music]
there was a week on the road terror yeah
we should know
remember constants memory honor the past
can remember supercruise refused to
engage supercruise does this here at all
get if we could just make a drive
without the lanes all would drive so
well hate the lanes like it's fine on
turns without the legs you just dream
about
Oh everybody like a near where we need
to go yep surely not I should show this
gobies where we're going yeah oh good
the models working well right here yeah
there's just some bog back there we'll
fix up
check the ground truth
open toward that accent
whereas right here I'm holding I'm
disappointed with this model don't worry
no sorry it's gonna be forever no
new models I live it doesn't wobble on
the highway like it's more sharp in its
decisions they're just sometimes wrong